第三楼字幕网www.disanlou.org
网友共享字幕仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
你吃完早餐了吗？
You done
with your breakfast?
是的
Yeah.
那走吧
Let's do this thing.
- 回头见。 - 好的。
I'll see you later.
Okay.
-小心开车。 -再见，妈妈。
Drive safe.
Bye, Mom.
- 你带午餐了吗？ - 是的。
- You got your lunch?
- Yeah.
Peterson夫人？
Mrs. Peterson?
是的。请问什么事？
Yes. Can I, um,help you?
我叫David，Peterson夫人。
My name is David,
Mrs. Peterson.
我，哦……
I, uh...
我认识您儿子，Caleb
I knew your son Caleb.
我们一起训练，一起服役
We trained together and served together
并且成为好朋友
and, uh, well, we came to be good friends.
噢，哦……
Oh, um...
你想进来吗？
Would you like to come inside?
谢谢！夫人
Thank you, ma'am.
你需要点儿什么吗？
So, are you sure I can't get you anything?
或许喝点水，那就很好
Mmm-hmm. Maybe just some water would be nice.
你怎么到这儿的？
How did you get here?
跑步
I ran.
我需要锻炼
I needed the exercise.
从巴士站，我意思，从城里
From the bus station, I mean, in town.
你跑了整段路？
You ran that whole way?
是的，夫人
Yes, ma'am.
给你
Here you go.
好的，谢谢夫人
All right. Thank you, ma'am.
你什么时候出来的？
When did you get out?
哦，我周三刚退伍
Well, I was discharged on Wednesday
从Fort Kennilworth直接来了这儿
and I came straight here from Fort Kennilworth.
你直接先来了这儿？
You came straight here first thing?
是啊，我应该尽快过来，但我还得回去
Yeah. I wanted to come by sooner, but I couldn't get leave.
为什么？
Why?
噢，我退伍是因为我受伤了
Well, I was discharged 'cause I was wounded.
我还得在部队医院住一阵子
I was in a military hospital for a bit,
也没什么要紧的
so it wasn't really the kind of thing
所以能离开
you could get leave from.
别担心，只是还有些弹片在背上
Ah, but don't worry, it was just a bit of shrapnel in my back.
很快就能好
I'm right as rain now.
我意思，为何你先来了这儿？
No, I meant, urn, why did you come here first thing?
哦，就像我说的，我和你儿子Caleb，我们……
Ah, well, like I said, me and your son Caleb, we were, uh...
我们非常亲密
We were pretty close.
他死时我跟他在一起
I was with him when he died.
- 真的？ - 是的，夫人
- Really? - Yes, ma'am.
他请求我来看望你
And one of the things he asked was for me to check on you all.
你和你的全家人
You and your whole family here. Uh...
他要我告诉你，他爱你
He wanted me to tell you that he loved you.
他还特别让我告诉每个人
He specifically wanted me to tell each one of you that
他爱你们
he loved you and
他一直思念你们知道最后
he was thinking of you guys up until the end.
我说我一定做到。于是，我来了
I said I'd do that and so, here I am.
请原谅我
Would you excuse me, please?
那是我
That's me.
就在那儿
Right there.
哦，是的
Well, I'll be...
我记得那一天
I remember that day.
我没有让你心烦吧？夫人
It wasn't my intention to upset you, ma'am.
或许我应该提前打个电话
I probably should have called first,
只是我还没有手机
but I don't own a cell phone yet
并且，我想，我只是没考虑
and, um, I guess, I just wasn't thinking.
就直接过来了
I'm going to be on my way now,
如果你愿意我们可以写e-mail
but I'd like it if we could exchange e-mails...
等等，别
Wait. No.
Anna，Caleb的妹妹，她上夜班
Anna, Caleb's sister, she works nights,
她睡的晚
and she sleeps late.
我想她一定愿意跟你见面
And I know she would love to meet you.
你能不能等会儿再走？
Would you stay a little while longer?
噢，你不会只是说客气话吧
Oh, you're not just saying that to be polite now?
你没必要这样
'Cause you don't need to be.
我不是，请留下……
No, I'm not. Please, stay. It's...
我很高兴你来这儿
It's nice having you here
我也很愿意听听你和Caleb更多的事
and I would love to hear more about you and Caleb.
好吧
Well, all right.
……Caleb和我，我们认为那声音
...Caleb and me, we figure that sounds, uh,
更多像是另外一种挑战
more like a challenge than anything else.
那晚他睡着后
So, uh, that night after he falls asleep,
我们挤了整管胶水在他床上
we kind of crept over to his cot with a tube of superglue.
哦，不！
Oh, no!
我们没对他做太坏的事
We didn't do anything too bad to him,
尽管我们可以，你知道
though, uh, we could have, you know.
嗨，你来了，Anna，这是David
Hey, there you are. Anna, this is David.
很高兴见到你
Very nice to meet you.
Caleb告诉我很多你的事
Caleb told me a lot about you.
David这周刚刚退役
David just got discharged this week.
他是你哥哥的朋友
He was a friend of your brother's.
你认识Caleb？
You knew Caleb?
是啊，女士
Yes, ma'am.
“是啊，女士”
"Yes, ma'am"
好吧
Okay.
那么，你住在哪儿？
So, um, where are you staying?
我注意到有个汽车旅馆就在高速路旁边……
Well, I noticed a motel off the highway on the way here...
不不，你在这儿时可以跟我们住一起
No, no, no, no. You will stay with us while you're here.
不，我不能打扰你们
Oh, no. I couldn't put you all out.
瞎说，我们愿意你住这儿，有足够的房间
Nonsense. We would love to have you. We have plenty of room.
其实，你可以住Caleb的房间
In fact, you can stay in Caleb's old room.
我们坚持
We insist.
好吧，恭敬不如从命
Well, I won't argue.
就一晚
Just for tonight, though.
我得去餐馆上班了
Well, I've got to head to the diner.
真的很高兴认识你
It was really great meeting you.
我也是，高兴认识你
Likewise. Very nice meeting you.
估计晚点儿还能见面
I guess I'll see you later. Bye.
哦
Um...
我带你看看房间吧
Can I show you to your room?
好啊
Great.
浴室里有干净的毛巾
There are clean towels in the bathroom
如果你想洗个澡
if you'd like to freshen up.
peterson夫人，确定我留下你没觉得不舒服？
Mrs. Peterson, are you sure you're comfortable with me staying in here?
当然
Of course.
我意思，这房间也用不上
I mean, it's not like it's going to any use.
我想这对我们都是好事
I think it could be a good thing for us.
哦……
Uh...
我先离开，你收拾吧
I'm gonna go and let you get settled in.
如果需要什么，就喊一声
If you need anything, just holler.
噢，上帝
Oh, my God!
Fucking pussy.
噢，上帝
Oh, my God!
Oh.
没事啊，宝贝儿，别哭
Oh, it's okay, little baby, don't cry. Aw.
嗨
Hey, there.
今天怎么样？
How was your day?
不错
It was good.
很好
Great.
……未免也太偶然，我不喜欢这样
...giving him a chance, it's that I don't like the idea of
随便邀请大街上个家伙留下
some random guy off the street being invited to stay
跟我的家人在一起
in my house with my family.
那么，你认识我哥哥？
So, you knew my brother?
认识，还很熟，是的
I did, pretty well, yeah.
他让我告诉你们，他爱你们
He wanted me to tell you that he loved you.
噢，谢谢！
Oh. Thanks.
……即使他说是Caleb的朋友
Even though he says he was friends with Caleb.
他在Caleb小队的照片里
He's in the photograph of Caleb's squad.
你看了照片
You saw the photograph.
- 他不是陌生人。- 你知道吗？
He was not a stranger. You know what?
如果他有创伤综合症
What if he has the PTSD
或者其他什么呢？
or whatever it's called?
一些像他这样的家伙回来都有心理健康问题，Laura
Some of these guys come back with mental health problems, Laura.
你有没有考虑这些？
Did you take that into account?
如果Caleb回来也不一样了呢？
What if Caleb had come back different?
你是不是也考虑了？
Did you take that into account?
哇，那可真是……哼……
Wow, that is... Hmm...
你父母为我在吵架
Your parents are fighting about me.
是啊，吵的很凶
Yeah. They argue a lot.
Huh.
看起来你好像受了伤
You look like you got hit or something.
是啊，体育课踢足球碰伤的
Yeah, yeah, I got hit with a football in gym class.
是啊，经常的事
Yeah, that can happen.
Yeah.
不不，你是对的，让我们跟他谈谈
No, no, you're right, you're right. Let's talk to him.
嗨，好吧
Hi, great, okay.
David，我们很高兴你在这儿
David, we're very happy to have you here.
晚饭前我要喝瓶啤酒，你要吗？
I'm gonna have a beer before dinner.
Can I offer you one?
- 哦，不了，谢谢！ - 好吧，你随便。
Well, no, thank you.
No. Okay. Suit yourself.
晚餐一个小时内就好
And dinner is gonna be ready in an hour.
那么Luke，为什么你不去做功课呢
So, Luke, why don't you do some homework.
好吧
Okay-
David，你需要什么吗？
David, can I get you anything?
不了，谢谢你Peterson夫人，我很好
Oh, no, thank you, Mrs. Peterson, I'm fine.
耶，接招
Yeah, hit this.
小心
Look out... Shit.
No...
不，我很好，谢谢
Now? No, I'm good, but thank you.
那么，你哥哥的朋友，他就留在这儿？
So, that friend of your brother's,
is he sticking around?
不知道，希望不是
I don't know. I hope not.
为什么？你说你喜欢他
Why? You said you liked him.
我说他看起来和善，这可是不同的
I said he seemed nice. That's not the same thing.
Oh, okay.
你为啥喜欢他？
Why don't you like him?
我没有喜欢他
I don't not like him.
只是，我……
It's just, I...
我意思，你了解Caleb
I mean, you kind of knew Caleb.
我们都……
We've all...
我只知道爸妈试着向前看
I just know Mom and Dad have been trying to move on
不像是想有太多回忆在这个镇子
and it's not like they don't have
enough reminders in this town.
Yeah.
我不知道，只是觉得太正常了
I don't know, that seems pretty normal to me.
你知道，孩子死了，那可很难啊
You know, like, your kid dies. That's hard.
Yeah.
或许我们只是不需要一个走着、呼吸着的提醒者
Guess we just don't need
a walking, breathing reminder
如同现在，你知道
of him right now, you know?
是啊，绝对
Yeah. Totally.
我得走了
I've got to go.
嘿，等下，等下
Hey, wait a second. Wait a second.
- 别，我不能。- 什么？
Stop. I can't... What!
不不，再呆会儿，就一会儿
No, no. Let's just hang out,
like, a little bit longer.
- 我不能。 - 就一会儿。
I can't. Just a little bit longer.
不行，我得走了
I can't. Mmm-mmm. I have to go.
- 你没必要非得走。 - 不，我得走
You don't have to go.
Yes, I do.
我们应该有时间明天在Kristen家见面，好吗？
But I'm sure we can find some time
at Kristen's tomorrow, okay?
Hmm.
停，我得走了
Stop, I have to go.
正弦是船锚的直角
The sine is the angle of the ship's anchor cable,
那么电缆是直角三角形的斜边
so the cable is the hypotenuse,
那么我们如何计算出
and what we need to find out
到海底的距离
is the distance down to the ocean bottom,
那是对立面，看见没？
so that's the opposite. Do you see?
不是吧
Not really.
你应该很聪明吧
So, you're kind of smart, huh?
我想是吧
I guess so.
嘿，工作怎样？
Hey, how was work?
还行，不忙
Good. Not too busy.
David，来瓶啤酒吗？
David, sure I can't get you a beer?
好吧，来一瓶，谢谢
You know, I will have one. Thank you.
- 我也要
- 是啊，就知道你也要
- I'll take one, too.
- Yeah, I'm sure you will.
再一个月我就21岁了
I'm 21 in a month.
那你就可以喝掉所有的啤酒了
You can have all the beer you want then,
如果你自己买的话
assuming you buy it yourself.
你帮他做作业？
Are you helping him with his homework?
不全是
Well, not exactly.
嘿，别走，呆会儿，聊聊
Hey, don't go. Stick around, be sociable.
有点累了，我得躺下了
Ugh, I'm kind of tired. I think I'm gonna lay down.
好吧，随便了
Okay. Suit yourself.
但是Allan,他名字叫Allan
But Allan, his name's Allan,
他来了只有，什么
he's only been there for, what,
差不多4年，但他却晋级了
like, four years, but he's got a degree,
于是“砰”，突然他就成地区经理了，我不是
so, boom, suddenly he's regional manager and I'm not.
没关系，我是说，无所谓
And that's okay. I mean, it's okay.
但我了解Laura，我知道她担心
But I know Laura, I know she's worried.
她怀疑我究竟
She wonders if I'm ever,
还能不能挣到钱
ever going to make any money.
你妻子是尊重你的，先生
Your wife seems to respect you, sir.
噢，是的
Oh, yeah. Yeah.
这倒是，你知道
It is what it is, you know.
那么你怎么样？有什么计划？
What about you, though? What about you? What are your plans?
想着明天去坐巴士
Figured I'd get on a bus tomorrow,
向南去佛罗里达或什么地方
head down to Florida or something
开始找份工作
and start looking for work.
我以前是做建筑工程的
I've done construction work before.
所以，我确定我能找到
So, I'm sure I'll find something.
不不，太疯狂了
No, no, no, no, no. That's crazy.
太疯狂，你都不知道要去哪里
That's crazy. You don't know where you're going.
留下来多呆几天
Stay here for a couple more days.
不，我不能
No. No, I can't.
我不能再利用你们的好意，先生
I couldn't impose on your hospitality any longer, sir.
你没有……对我们利用……
You're not... Impose on our...
先生？你称呼我先生？
And "sir"? You're calling me "sir" now?
别再叫我先生，我的名字是Spencer
You gotta stop with the "sir," my name's Spencer.
你必须叫我Spencer，天啊
You gotta call me Spencer, for God sakes.
Okay-
好吧
All right. Okay.
那么你就呆在这一带，对吗？
So you're sticking around, right?
你呆在这儿至少等到你知道要去哪儿
You stick around at least till you know where you're going.
好吧，或许就几天，好吗？
Well, maybe just a couple more days, all right.
好极了，说定了
Cool, excellent. It's a deal.
让我们再喝两瓶庆祝下
Let's have a couple more of these to celebrate,
然后我就得上床了
and then I've got to get off to bed.
天，把你的酒喝完
God, you can put your liquor away.
我想是的
I guess so.
我累了，你累吗？
I'm tired. Are you tired?
不，我还不想睡
No, I don't need much sleep.
你在这儿干什么？
What are you doing here?
我告诉你妈妈今天我来学校接你
I told your mom I could pick you up
from school today.
好不好？
That cool?
Yeah.
你不像是有什么朋友啊
Don't you, like, have any friends?
我有很多朋友
I have lots of friends.
只是，不在这。在网上。
Just not, like, here. Like, online.
Oh.
你在等什么？
What are you waiting for?
我要你指给我昨天谁打了你
I want you to show me who hit you yesterday.
我是踢足球碰伤的
I got hit with a football.
Yeah.
你打算做什么？
What are you going to do?
不坏的事
Nothing bad.
那边
Over there.
全都是？
All of them?
哦，看起来他们给我出了个难题
Well, most of them give me a hard time.
那两个，Mike和Ian，是最坏的
Those two guys, Mike and Ian, are the worst.
这俩家伙是真正的混蛋
Those guys are real assholes.
能走了吗？
Can we go now?
是
Yes.
你在干什么？
What are you doing?
他们要去酒吧
They're going to a bar?
Uh, yeah,
这地方只服务足球队的人
this place will serve you if you're on the football team.
好吧，我想去喝一杯
Well, I could use a drink.
你怎么样？
How about you?
不
No.
来吗？
You coming?
不
No.
好吧，如果你改主意了，我就在里面
Well, I'll be inside if you change your mind.
见鬼？
What the fuck?
嗨，Luke
Hey, Luke.
可能是他的男朋友什么的
Maybe it's his boyfriend or something?
对不起
Excuse me.
我需要看看身份证
I'm gonna need to see some ID.
所有人的身份证？
You ID all of them?
你要点什么？
What can I get you?
你知道怎么做个火球吗？
Do you know how to make a fireball?
肉桂杜松子酒加辣椒酱
Cinnamon schnapps and Tabasco sauce.
那就是我要的酒，来一杯
That's my drink of choice. Let me get one of those.
给我弟弟来瓶可乐
A Coke here for my brother,
我不禁注意到
and I can't help but notice
那边一些女生再喝便宜的啤酒
that those ladies over there are drinking cheap beer.
这让我觉得有点惭愧
That seems like a shame to me.
我愿意给她们每人买一份blowjob shot
I'd like to buy each one of them a blowjob shot.
注：blowjob shot，一种用酒、饮料、奶油调制的饮品，
盛在小酒杯中，不用手，直接用嘴叼起，仰脖饮下，状似口交。
- 你是认真的？ - 是的。
Are you serious?
I am, yes.
那你愿意给那几个小伙子买点什么吗？
Do you wanna buy anything for their fellas?
我看起来像喜欢给那几个小伙子买东西的吗？
Do I look like I'd like to buy something for their fellas?
可能会显得比较礼貌
Might be the polite thing to do.
好吧
Sure, okay, fine.
给他们每人一杯大都会鸡尾酒
I'm gonna get each one of those guys a cosmopolitan.
先生，我不知道你是为了什么
Mister, I don't know what you're going for,
不过我想着只是啤酒
but, uh, I was thinking a beer.
不，blowjob shot给女士
No. Blowjob shots for the ladies,
大都会鸡尾酒给那几个家伙
and a cosmopolitan for each of the guys.
不用找钱了
You keep the change on that.
你说了算
You got it.
你很富有吗？
Are you, like, rich?
钱是容易挣的
Cash is easy to get.
他不需要穿上衣服
He doesn't need to be in costume
把自己装成个屁股
to make an ass out of himself.
你的可乐，你的火球
Here's your Coke, here's your fireball.
他们的酒马上就好
Got their shots and cosmos coming right up.
谢谢
Thank you.
你要不要试试？
You want to try it?
好
Sure.
天啊！
God!
这干脆就是辣椒
It's like hot peppers.
噢，你喜欢喝这个？
Ugh, you drink that?
是的
Yep.
噢！
Ah!
你是怎么做到的？
How do you do that?
习惯就好了
You get used to it.
那边桌子那位给的
From that table over there.
那个家伙？
That fucking guy?
他们看起来很生气
They look annoyed.
是的
Yep.
谢谢你的酒
Thanks for the drink.
不客气
You're welcome.
Mmm.
我不想要，不过，你可以
I don't want it, though. You can have it.
可能你更喜欢这个
Well, maybe you prefer this.
噢，我的眼睛
Ow! My eyes!
嘿，你……
Hey, you...
嘿，Luke
Hey, Luke.
Luke.
不错
Cool.
你俩应该离开了
You guys should get out of here.
报警并且告诉警察事实
Call the police and tell them the truth.
一帮学校的孩子来这儿了
A gang of high school kids came in here
要求你提供酒
and demanded you serve them drinks.
你试着检查身份证
Well, you tried to ID them,
但他们威胁找麻烦
but, uh, they threatened to cause trouble.
发生了打斗
There was a fight.
你并没有仔细看清其他家伙的脸
You didn't really get a good look at the other guys.
另外，我想你这个地方
Otherwise, I imagine you and this place
可能会因为服务未成年人而有麻烦
could get into trouble for serving minors.
我意思
I mean,
这迟早会发生
this is what happens.
这儿
Here.
是损坏赔偿
For the damages.
Luke！怎么了？
Luke! What happened?
在学校跟人打架了
I got into a fight with some guys at school.
- 你没事吧？ - 是的，没事。
Are you okay? Yeah, I'm fine.
几个成年人打了我，没什么大不了的
Some seniors were picking on me. It's no big deal.
为什么选中你？
Why were they picking on you?
我不知道，我要回房间了，好了
I don't know, okay. I'm just going to go
to my room, all right.
他没事吧？
Is he all right?
是的，夫人，没事
Yes, ma'am, he's fine.
他在学校惹了什么麻烦吗？
Did he get in trouble at the school?
不，每人看见，只是高中那点事，你懂的
No, no one saw. It's just the usual
high school stuff, you know.
我告诉他会教他如何自卫
I told him I'd teach him some self-defense
如果他觉得需要的话
when he's feeling up to it.
我确定那正是他需要的
I'm sure that's exactly what he needs.
有你在那儿我就放心了
Well, l am very relieved that you were there.
我准备去Kristen家了
I'm going to get ready for Kristen's.
Anna，我们能在厨房谈下吗？
Anna, can we talk in the kitchen?
当然
Sure.
请原谅
Excuse us.
什么？
What?
邀请他去Party
Invite him to the party.
- 为什么？ - 因为他就一个人，宝贝儿
- Why? - 'Cause he's lonely, sweetie.
Caleb也会高兴的
Caleb would really love that
真的？你确定这样？
Really? You're going to pull that card?
是的
Yes.
David，你愿意今晚跟我一起去Party吗？
David, would you like to come to the party with me tonight?
好啊，听起来不错
Sure, that sounds nice.
很好，我将在7点钟出发
Great. I'm going to leave around 7:00.
好的
All right.
Luke，我要洗澡
Luke, I need to take a shower.
Luke!
Luke，快点，我得……
Luke, come on, I need to...
对不起……
I'm sorry, uh...
不，我很抱歉
Um, no, I'm sorry,
我以为Luke在里面
I thought Luke was in there.
我想我们该穿衣服了
Oh, I guess I better go get dressed.
是的
Yeah, yeah.
你应该，应该穿了
You should, um, probably do that.
那么，也没什么大不了的
So, um, this isn't a big deal or anything,
这地方不仅仅是Kristen的地方
but this isn't just Kristen's place.
我男朋友，Zeke,也住这儿
My boyfriend, Zeke, lives here, too.
我不知道你有男朋友
I didn't know you had a boyfriend.
对的，我父母也不知道
Yeah, well, neither do my parents.
我不介意保持这个秘密，如果你觉得酷的话
And I wouldn't mind keeping it that way,
if that's cool with you.
我不会说一个字
I won't say anything.
这不关我的事
It's none of my business.
Hi.
Hey.
嘿，这是谁？
Hey, who's this?
这是David，他是我哥哥Caleb的朋友
Um, this is David, he was friends with my brother Caleb.
- 我曾跟你说起过。 - 你好吗！
I told you about him.
How do you do?
很好，谢谢
Mmm, fine, thank you.
Zeke在里面爽呢，他正等着有人帮他搬酒桶
Zeke's inside smoking. He was waiting for help
to carry the kegs.
我可以搬进来
I'll bring them in.
在哪儿？
Where are they?
在Zeke的面包车里，应该没锁
They're in Zeke's van. It should be unlocked.
Anna?
不，今晚不行，我倒是想……
No. I can't tonight. I wish.
什么？真的？
What? Really?
什么？你家的客人？
What? Your houseguest?
是的，他是……
Yeah, he's...
打算放哪儿？
Where do you want these?
就放这儿吧
Well, you can set them right here.
欢迎来到Party
My man, welcome to the party.
Craig, 别！
Craig, no.
没事的，他是个大男孩儿
It's fine. He's a big boy.
当然
Sure.
谢谢
Thanks.
谢谢你
Thank you.
对不起
Excuse me.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你没事吧？
You all right?
我很好
Yeah, I'm fine.
你要不要……
You wanna...
好的，走
Yeah, let's go.
妈的
God damn it.
他们是谁？
Who are they?
我的前任，这我刚刚告诉你
No. That's my ex. The one I was just telling you about.
嘿，我得跟你谈谈
Hey, I need to talk to you.
我正忙着，Drew
I'm busy right now, Drew.
我整个星期都在给你打电话
I've been calling you all week,
然后，我听说你今晚有个Party？
and then I hear you're having a party tonight?
怎么回事？
What the fuck?
我正跟朋友说话，你很没礼貌
I'm talking to my friend. You're being rude.
好吧，听着，只是……
All right, listen, just...
过来
Come here...
你他妈的
Motherfucker!
把他弄出去
Get him out of here.
抱歉你的照片
Sorry about your picture.
不，别放在心上
No, don't worry about it.
你……
Did you, um...
你想不想看看其他的房间？
Did you want to see the rest of the house?
没事吧？
Are you okay?
是的，怎么？
Yeah. Why?
看起来你好像不喜欢
Seems like you're not really into this.
哦，我喜欢
Oh, I am.
Oh...
的确
You are.
嘿，你在这儿
Hey, there they are.
你有什么？我有王后，他有大王
Who have you got? I got a queen. He's got a king.
坐下
Sit down.
还以为你离开Party了，找到了更有趣的
Thought you guys left your own party, found something better.
- 来点儿？ - 不，我很好
Want some? No, I'm good.
我只是……
I just...
我想说我们挺你这家伙
I wanted to say we support you guys.
如果你需要什么，就告诉我
If you need anything, you just let me know.
怎么挺？
Support us how?
我意思你知道，我们挺你
I mean, you know, we support you,
就像，“冲啊美国！”，对吧？
like, "Go America!" right?
但你不会支持我，比如，招募？
But you wouldn't support us by, like, enlisting?
Aw...
妈的，哥们儿，他们不让我进入
Shit, man, they don't want me in there.
我不能，你知道
No, I can't, you know.
我惹了一堆烂事
I've got bad asthma.
让我觉得很难……
It'd make it real hard to...
很难什么？
Hard to what?
嘿，哥们儿，我意思，我只是……
Hey, man, I mean, I just...
什么？
What'?
我只是逗逗你，哥们儿
I'm just fucking with you, man.
妈的，哥们儿
Fuck, man.
你觉得这很逗乐，是吗Kristen？
Oh, you think that's funny, huh, Kristen?
我会儿回来
I'll be right back.
多好的两片屁股，啊？
Nice piece of ass there, huh?
你能给我搞把枪吗？
Could you get me a gun?
枪？
A gun?
是的，我可以搞把枪
Yeah, I can get you a gun.
你要枪干嘛？
What do you need a gun for?
我是当兵的，哥们儿，我喜欢枪
I'm a soldier, man. I like guns.
好吧，我认识个家伙
Yeah. I know a guy.
有钱吗？
You got cash?
是的
I do.
妈的，给我电话号码
Fuck it. Give me your number.
我正用这个一次性的
I'm using a burner right now.
号码在背面
Number's on the back.
大兵喜欢枪
Soldiers like guns.
让我出面可有点难为我
Landing a gig is huge for me.
要是我出门了呢？
What's the big deal if I go on tour?
比如，三个星期，最多
It's, like, three weeks, max.
为什么你不相信我，哪怕5秒钟
Why don't you trust me for, like, five seconds?
我不知道，也许……
I don't know. Maybe...
- 你没有理由不相信我。
- 好了打住吧
I've given you no reason not to trust me.
I'm done with this.
不要这样
Come on.
- 准备走吗？
- 好的
You ready to go?
Sure.
- 我开车
- 不，我没事
I'll drive.
No, I'm fine.
我开
I'll drive.
你醉了
You're stoned.
你比我好很多吗？
And how are you more sober than me?
我比你大
I'm bigger than you.
拜托，系上安全带
Please, put on your seat belt.
- 你想谈谈吗？
- 不
Do you want to talk about it?
No.
只是……
It's just...
没什么，只是我们有点不同意见
It's nothing. I mean, we got into an argument.
以前的事
It's old stuff.
你知道他在乐队时我曾爱过他
You know, I used to love that he was in a band.
但现在我正在为上大学攒钱
But now I'm saving money for college,
但他却不思进取
and he just isn't moving on.
我意思，他甚至都没份工作
I mean, he doesn't even have a job.
他是毒品贩子
Well, he's a drug dealer.
得了，他不是毒品贩子
Okay. He's not a drug dealer.
是的，有时候卖点儿，卖给朋友赚点儿零花
Yeah. He sells drugs sometimes to, like, friends for extra cash.
如果他不珍惜跟你在一起，他就是个傻子
Well, if he's messing things up with you,
then he's a fool,
你也无需为此烦心
and you don't need to worry about it.
我是认真的
No. I'm serious.
我意思，如果我能拥有你这样的女孩儿
I mean, hell, if I'd had a girl
like you back home,
我不会跑到中东去挨枪子儿
I wouldn't have gone over to the
Middle East to get shot at.
谢谢
Thank you.
我喜欢这音乐
I like this music.
真的？
You do?
这是混合我喜欢的刻在一张碟上
It's, uh, just a mix that I made.
如果你喜欢我可以刻张给你
I can make you one if you wanted.
真的？能把这首歌刻进去吗？
Yeah? Can you put this song on it?
当然，可以
Yeah, I can do that.
那么，晚安
So, um, good night.
晚安
Good night.
谢谢邀请我出去
Thanks for inviting me out.
没问题
Yeah, no problem.
晚安
Good night.
第三楼字幕网www.disanlou.org
网友共享字幕仅供翻译交流使用, 禁止用于商业用途
不，我想继续我们的讨论
No. I want to proceed as we discussed.
每人能认出我，这很重要
No one will be able to recognize me.
That's important.
什么意思？“牙科记录”？
What do you mean, "Dental records"?
整牙医生？不，我不需要
An orthodontist? No, I don't need that.
手指头，对
Fingers, yes.
越快越好，我得挂断了
As soon as possible. I'm off the grid for now.
恐怕有人在试着找我
But there are people trying to look for me.
我明白需要时间，但这很紧迫
I understand it'll take some time,
but this is urgent.
我只是需要张新面孔
I just need a new face.
我会保留这部手机防止有事发生，你需要跟我联系
I'll keep this phone in case anything comes up
and you need to reach me.
好了，挂了
All right. Copy that.
是的，他的名字叫David Anderson Collins
Yeah, his name is David Anderson Collins.
我能告诉你他服役部队的变化，如果有帮助
I can tell you the unit that
he served in if that helps.
不，没什么事，哦……
No, nothings wrong. Um...
他是我哥哥的朋友，我们听说他回来了
He was friends with my brother
and we heard that he was back,
任何联系方式都是好的
so, uh, any contact information would be great.
OK，女士，如果有消息我会打电话
Okay, ma'am. I'll call you when
we have any details.
再见
Good bye.
机密档案
立刻联系KPG Corporation
告诉他们，David Collins已经死了
Tell Fort Kennilworth that David Collins is dead.
只告诉他们官方版本
Just give them the official version.
我马上就去
We'll take it from here.
下周我将会见其他委员会成员
Next week I'm meeting with the rest of the board
讨论我们和军方未来的工作
to discuss the future of our work with the military,
鉴于伊奥利亚计划已经终止
in light of Project Aegolius' dissolution.
关于此Richard有更多的信息汇报
Richard has more information
on that subject. Richard?
我不会披露太多信息
I can't get into too many details,
即使你们要求
nor would you want me to.
不过，我可以说……
However, I can say that...
抱歉打断你，有事情发生
Sorry to interrupt. Somethings come up.
非常抱歉，请各位原谅
My apologies, but you'll have to excuse me.
什么时候接到Fort Kennilworth电话的？
When did Fort Kennilworth receive this call?
大概一小时前
About an hour ago, sir.
有打电话者的身份吗？
Have you lD'd the caller?
还没确认，不过她给了名字Anna Peterson
Not confirmed, but she gave
her name as Anna Peterson.
Peterson
Peterson.
跟Caleb Peterson有关系？
As in Caleb Peterson?
他妹妹
His sister.
地址在这儿
Home address is in there.
给我订下班飞机
Book me on the next flight.
如果需要任何许可，去搞定
If we need to charter something, do it.
再带上几个狙击手
And I'm gonna need some shooters.
如果有人问起发生了什么，我怎么说？
If anyone asks what's happening,
what do I tell them?
粉饰一切
Make something up.
没有圈子外的人知道这个机划仍在继续
No one outside this circle can know that any of
our subjects are still active.
如果KPG有人想在此事上退缩
If KPG gets any blowback on this,
你和我就都完蛋了
you and I will both be hung out to dry.
明白？
You got that?
Mmm.
机票订好给我打电话
Call me when you got the plane booked.
我没有晚吧
I'm not late, am l?
没有，时间刚刚好
No, no. You're just on time.
好的
Good.
你看，在开始之前
Look, before we get started,
我只是想确认你已经带了钱
I just want to make sure that you've got some cash on you.
不想冒犯
No offense.
这可以吧？
That should be good?
可以
It'll do.
开始吧
Let's get started.
从这开始
Let's start with this.
我是说，这是把标准贝瑞塔
I mean, it's a standard Beretta.
我相信你一定很熟悉
I'm sure you're familiar with it.
不要以为，你看了这把，也就看了全部
In my opinion, if you've seen one of these,
you've seen them all.
这件宝贝，这是
But this baby, this here is
9毫米Wintness Elite精英
a 9-millimeter Witness Elite.
看起来跟贝瑞塔很相似
It's a very similar weapon to the Beretta,
但我更喜欢这把枪的后座力
but I prefer the recoil.
我意思，你绝对感觉不到震动
I mean, it's got absolutely no kick at all.
当兵的？
You army?
Yes, sir.
我是海军
I'm navy, myself.
很好
Yeah, that's fine.
你要这把精英？
You want the Elite?
噢，我要全部
Oh, I'll take 'em all.
所有的手枪？
All the handguns?
不，所有的，你全部的枪。
No. Everything. All your guns.
妈的
Shit.
跟我想的一样
That's what I was thinking.
瞧，哥们儿，如果你带了足够的钱
Look, man, if you've brought money for all of them,
我就给你打个折，把枪全拿走
I'll cut you a deal. You can take 'em
all off my hands.
不，我打算杀了你
No, I'm going to kill you.
嘿，搞什么鬼，David？
Hey, what the fuck, David?
你听我讲他妈的最后一句
Now, you listen to me one fucking second...
等等
Wait, wait, wait.
不，不
No, no, no, no.
喂？
Hello?
对，谢谢你打回电话给我
Yeah, thanks for calling me back.
什么？
What?
嗨，妈妈，我能跟你说句话吗？
Hey, Mom, can I talk to you for a second?
当然，宝贝儿，怎么了？
Sure, sweetie, what's going on?
噢，我给军方基地打了电话
Um, I called the army base
David说他刚从那儿退役
that David said that he was just discharged from,
我想跟他们谈谈
I wanted to ask about him.
什么？为啥要这样做？
What? Why would you do that?
Spencer?
我得喝一杯
I need a drink.
- 为什么？发生什么了？
- 让我先喝一杯，亲爱的
Why? What happened?
I'm getting a drink, honey.
他们找到了Allan，你知道我的老板Allan吧？
They found Allan, you know my boss, Allan?
他失踪了好多天了
He'd been missing from work for a couple of days,
每个人都很担心
everybody got very worried
他的一个朋友破门而入
so one of his friends went over and broke
into his house.
发现他和他的女朋友都死了
And they found him and his girlfriend dead.
他俩都吞了大把的药丸
They'd both taken a bunch of prescription pills,
看起来像是一起自杀了
it was like they committed suicide together or something.
噢，我的天
Oh, my God!
但这可有点说不通啊，他……
But that doesn't make any sense. He was...
是啊，那家伙看起来完全正常
No. The guy was totally normal.
警察正在调查，你知道，这是……
But the police are investigating. You know, it's, uh...
没看出有人闯入
Doesn't look like it was a break-in.
没有强行进入的痕迹
There was no forced entries.
她，哦……那女孩儿，她，哦……
She, uh... The girl... She had, uh...
她的身体有伤痕
She had bruises on her body.
我不明白怎么回事
I don't know what that means.
不管怎么样，只能交给警察处理了
Anyway, uh, we will leave it for the police
再告诉我们发生了什么
to tell us exactly what happened.
我不知道
I don't know.
讨厌的是，我将成为地区经理
Damn thing is this makes me regional manager.
是的，他们最快速度给我打了电话
Yeah. As soon as Corporate found out,
they called me.
他们让我立刻从明天开始
Right away they want me to start tomorrow.
并且会支付跟Allan同样的薪水
And they're offering me Allan's salary.
那..
So...
那是，哦……
that's, uh...
Yeah.
仔细想想你需要什么
Careful what you wish for.
David.
抱歉打断你们
I'm sorry to interrupt
不，别犯傻，没事
No. Don't be silly. It's fine.
噢，我正喝酒呢，你来点吗？
Um, I'm having a drink. Would you join me?
好的
Oh, sure.
我马上回来
I'll be right back.
Hello?
Hey, Anna?
是Craig，他们在采石场刚找到他
It's Craig, babe. They just found him out at the quarry.
他死了，有人射杀了他
He's dead. Someone shot him.
什么？
What?
他们知道是谁干的吗？
Do they know who did it?
我还不知道太多细节
I don't really have all the details yet.
晚点见面好吗？
Um, can you meet up later?
好的
Yeah, of course.
有点事我得告诉你
Um, there's something else I need to talk to you about.
什么事？
What is it?
噢，妈的
Oh, shit. Fuck.
我得挂了，好吧，我打电话给你
Babe, I got to go, all right. I'll call you back.
Hello?
我刚听Zeke说
I just heard from Zeke.
你怎么样？
How are you doing?
只是有点接受不了
I just don't get it.
谁会伤害Craig？
Who'd want to hurt Craig?
是啊，你能先坐下吗？
Yeah, I know. Can you sit down for a second?
是
Yeah.
你说怎么做来着？
So, how does this work again?
首先在顶部挖个洞
Uh, first you make a hole at the top,
你就能进入里面用勺子把瓤挖出来
so you can reach in and scoop all the guts out.
天啊
Oh, man.
你父母的刀子真恶心
Your parents' knives suck.
是
Yeah.
好多了
That's better.
你总是带着它吗？
Do you carry that with you, like, all the time?
哦，这个？是的
Oh, this thing? Sure.
为什么？
Why?
不知道
I don't know.
以防万一
Just in case.
我给David说离开的那个基地打了电话
I called the army base that David said that he was from.
他们告诉我David Collins一周前死了
They told me that David Collins died a week ago.
亚利桑那州一所军方医院
He was in some military hospital in Arizona.
氧气筒发生了爆炸
There was a fire from oxygen tanks.
大概20个人死了，David Collins是其中之一
About 20 people died, David Collins was one of them.
David有任何身份证件或者信用卡吗？
Does David have any ID? Credit cards?
我从没见过他有钱包
I've never seen him use a wallet.
他的电话呢？他有个一次性的，是吗？
What about his phone? He has a burner, right?
你怎么不查查他打过电话的号码？
Why don't you check some of the numbers he's called?
你弟弟懂电脑
Your brother knows computers.
看能不能找出什么？
Have him look some of them up.
对，是个好主意
Yeah. That's a good idea.
嘿，Kristen. 我觉得那一对想结账有一阵子了
Hey, Kristen. I think that couple's been done for a bit.
我来吧，谢谢
I've got it. Thanks.
下班后打电话给我
Call me after work, okay?
- 自己小心。 - 你也是
Take care of yourself.
You, too.
你想听听我的建议吗，Luke？
Do you want some advice, Luke?
Sure.
永远别让任何人作弄你
Never let anyone pick on you.
希望你能永远记住这一点
Otherwise, you'll carry it with
you the rest of your life.
学校的那些孩子，他们比你高大些？
Those kids at school, they're bigger than you?
Yeah.
那就带把刀去学校
Then bring a knife to school.
如果他们抢走了并且打了你
If they take it off of you and beat you up,
你就晚上到他们的房子
you go around their houses at night
一把火烧了那房子和里面的人
and burn them down with their families inside.
他们能做什么？
What's the worst they can do?
Yeah. Okay.
给，你留着
Here. You keep it.
你把这给我？
You're giving this to me?
是的，你的了，我还有其他的
Yeah, man, it's yours. I've got others.
谢谢
Thanks.
Hey.
爸妈在吗？
Mom and Dad around?
没，他们去商店了
No. They went to the store.
你妈妈做了南瓜派
Your mom's making pumpkin pie.
酷
That's cool.
吗的
Shit.
Fuck!
Fuck.
天阿
Oh, my God!
Hello.
Hey, it's, uh, me.
Hey.
什么？
What?
他们在你的面包车里找到了杀Craig的枪？
They found the gun that killed Craig in your van?
是的，这是嫁祸于我
Yeah, it was wiped clean.
我猜警察收到了匿名的报告
Um, I guess they just got an anonymous tip or something.
但你是无辜的
But you're innocent!
Anna，我知道，但他们又搜查了我的房间
Anna, I know, but' um, then they searched my room,
于是找到了些其他东东，你知道的
and they found some other stuff. You know.
所以，看起来我得在这儿呆一阵子了
So, it looks like I'm actually gonna be
here for a little while.
我爱你
I love you, all right?
我知道，我得挂了
Yeah, I know. I gotta go.
Okay -
爱你，拜
Love you, bye.
亲爱的，没事吧？
Honey, you okay?
I, um...
我得朋友Craig今天被杀了
My friend Craig was killed today.
噢，天啊，对不起
Oh, my God. I'm so sorry.
怎么了？发生了什么？
How? What happened?
他中枪了，我不知道
He was shot. I don't know.
为此他们逮捕了Zeke
And they arrested Zeke for it.
- Zeke?
- I'm sorry, honey.
但是如果他们逮捕了你的前任男朋友
But if they arrested your ex-boyfriend,
那多半有个很好的理由
it was probably for a very good reason.
我们都知道Zeke在这个社区并非什么好鸟
We all know Zeke was never exactly
a pillar of this community.
他不是我前任男朋友，爸爸，是现任男朋友
He's not my ex-boyfriend, Dad, he's my boyfriend.
我一直跟他在一起
I never stopped seeing him.
我已经20岁了，我可以跟任何人约会
I'm 20 years old, I can date who I want.
只要你还生活在这所房子里，就不能
As long as you live in this house, you cannot.
你并不了解他，一点也不了解
Oh, you know nothing about him! Nothing!
- 我知道他是个毒贩子和瘾君子……
- 是吗，爸爸！
I know he's a drugged-out punk junkie...
Really, Dad!
在我女儿17岁的时候
...who started
dating my daughter
就开始跟她约会，这就是我知道的
when she was 17 years old,
is what I know.
好吧
Right.
他怎么样呢？
What about him?
每个人最好的朋友
Everybody's best friend.
我给他说离开的基地打了电话
I called the military base that he said he was from
他们告诉我，他已经死了
and they told me he was dead.
哦，那对于你可是个军事情报
Ah, that's military intelligence for you.
好吧，看看他的身份证吧
Right. Ask to see his ID.
他不是David Collins，我们不知道他是谁
He's not David Collins, okay. We don't know who he is.
受伤之前我是特种部队的一员
I was part of a special forces
unit when I was injured,
所以他们会给你提供个封面故事
so they should be providing a cover story
如果一般平民问到我
if any civilians ask about me.
这是好事
That's a good thing.
但我没有拿我的军牌
But I did get my dog tags back.
Uh...
他们的在这儿
They're right here.
我不喜欢戴，因为……
I don't like to wear them because, uh...
我不知道，但是……
Well, I don't know, but, um...
我喜欢带着它们，尽管，你知道
I like having them with me, though, you know.
至于身份证，我没有一个目前的证明
As for ID, I don't have a current license,
但我有份文件在我包里，我是否应该去……
but, uh, I've got my documents in my bag.
Should I go...
不不，没那个必要
No, no, no. That won't be necessary.
Anna Peterson，你现在欠他一个道歉
Anna Peterson, you owe him an apology right now.
- 妈的没门儿
- 小心你的说话
No fucking way.
You watch your mouth, young lady.
关于你的朋友Craig，我十分抱歉
I am very sorry about your friend Craig.
发生这样的事的确可怕
That's a terrible thing that happened.
就目前来看，我可以负责人地说
As far as it goes with Zeke Hastings and his crew,
Zeke Hastings和他的团队
I have it on very good authority
毫无疑问是一帮毒贩子
they're nothing but a bunch of pot dealers.
你需要知道的只是他为何因为谋杀被捕
You wanna know why Zeke was arrested for murder?
或许他真干了，这就是为什么
Because he probably did it, that's why.
- Fuck you!
- Ugh.
Hey, now, Anna.
很抱歉，亲爱的。David，我很抱歉
I'm sorry, honey. David, I'm terribly sorry.
不，没什么，她只是……难受罢了
No, that's okay. She's, uh... She's upset.
我或许的确应该早点……
I probably should have explained
……解释清楚特种部队的事
the, uh, special forces thing earlier,
只是，我们没有想到会谈到这些事
it's just, we're not really supposed to talk about it.
不，我明白
No. I understand.
Uh...
我得再喝点儿，你呢，David？
I could use a drink. How about you, David?
Yes, please.
什么？
What?
Hey.
我只想说……
I just wanted to say, uh...
我只想说Craig的事我也感到很遗憾
I just wanted to say how sorry I am about Craig.
他看起来是个好人
He seemed like a really cool guy.
还有Zeke被捕…… 很抱歉
And Zeke getting arrested... Again, I'm very sorry.
在这紧张的时刻我知道你们并不需要我
I know you don't need me here at this stressful time.
没帮上忙我觉得羞愧
I'm not helping, which is a shame,
因为我答应Caleb我会……
because I promised Caleb I would do
……尽我所能帮助你的全家
anything I could to help your family.
但就这样你知道
But just so you know,
我会在几天之内搬走
I'll be moving on in a couple of days.
你不会再忍受我了，好吗？
So, you don't need to put up with me much longer, okay?
Okay.
Okay-
好
Good.
这是什么？
What is this?
给我刻的CD？
Is this the CD you made me?
是的
Um, yeah.
刻完了？
Is it done?
是的
Yeah.
好的，谢谢
Well, thank you.
等不及听听了
I can't wait to listen to it.
我要每个枪手在半径100英里以内
I want every contractor within a 100-mile radius.
不管他们从哪儿赶过来
And I don't care where they come from.
KPG的人、前军人，不管谁
KPG, ex-military, whatever.
我着陆的时候每支队伍都要动员起来
I'll need a team mobilized by the time l land.
我将会给每个人布置必需的任务
I'll give them the necessary mission specs in person.
不能冒任何风险让此事泄露
We can't risk a leak on this.
祝好运
Good luck.
你拍了David电话的照片？
You took a picture of Davids phone?
是的，我在网上付款
Yeah. I paid for a reverse directory thing
可以查出电话号码
to look the number up online.
说是一个迈阿密的医生的没有记录名册的号码
It said it was this unlisted landline of a doctor in Miami.
他的名字是Peter Boddington
His name's Peter Boddington.
此外他根本不是个医生
Except he's not a doctor anymore.
两年前他失去了执照
He lost his license two years ago
因为酒醉后给一名妇女做脸部整容
after performinga face lift on a woman
while he was drunk.
那么，David认识这家伙？我意思，或许是他的叔叔什么的
So, David knows the guy? I mean, maybe it's
his uncle or something.
我就是为什么我想搞清楚
That's what I'm trying to figure out.
我需要跟警察谈谈
I need to talk to the police.
警察在Zeke的房间找到了这些毒品
The cops found those drugs in Zeke's room,
所以警察认为他们抓对了人
so they think they've got their guy.
你需要我干什么？
So, what do you need me to do?
找到任何这家伙的信息
Get any information you can on this guy.
你确实觉得是David杀了Craig和另外那家伙
Do you really think David killed Craig
and that other guy?
是的
Yeah. I do.
好吧，我看看能不能发现什么
Okay. I'll see if I can find anything.
谢谢，Luke
Thank you, Luke.
抱歉，晚点我再给你看看一些魔术技巧
I'm sorry. I'll show you some magic tricks later. Just...
Um...
嘿，笨蛋
Hey, faggot.
嘿，你看的是什么？
Hey, what's that you're looking at?
Oh...
你在找人做变性手术吗？
Are you looking for someone to do your
sex change operation?
你这小婊子……
You little fucking bitch...
这就对了，母狗
That's right, bitches.
天啊
God damn it.
你怎么样？ 我没事。
Are you okay? I'm fine.
- Peterson夫人？
- 是我
Mrs. Peterson?
Yes, that's right.
Alston先生要见你，请进去吧
Mr. Alston will see you now. Please, step inside.
等一下
Okay. Just a second.
怎么了？
What happened?
这孩子叫我笨蛋
This kid called me a faggot,
所以，我
so l, uh,
在他脸上打断了尺子
broke a yardstick on his face.
Okay -
棒极了
Awesome.
我跟你一起进去
I'll go in with you.
Okay -
从这儿进去？
Is it this way?
Yes.
学校方面对于校园暴力是持零容忍态度的
Due to our school's zero tolerance
policy on violence,
对于开除您儿子我恐怕没有第二个选择
I'm afraid we have no choice
but to expel your son.
虽然还在等待董事会的决定
That's pending the decision of the board,
但我觉得恐怕已经确定无疑了
but I'm afraid it's fairly certain.
- 但…… - 我很抱歉
But...   I'm sorry.
那孩子叫他什么？
What did the kid call him?
什么？
What?
你知道的，那孩子，Luke打了脸的那一个
You know, the kid, the one Luke hit in the face.
他叫Luke什么？
What did he call Luke?
我不认为跟此事有什么相关
I don't think that's relevant to this conversation.
他是不是叫他笨蛋？
Did he call him a faggot?
我相信确实是用了这个词，但那并非借口……
I believe that's the word that was
used, yes. But that's no excuse...
不过，那造成了憎恨
So, that makes it a hate crime.
- 什么？ - 憎恨
What? A hate crime.
同时我也很想知道，还有多少其他孩子
And I'd like to know how many others
在您的监督之下如此对待她的儿子
have been perpetrated against her son
under your watch.
一个同性恋学生为了保护自己免受身体暴力的侵害
A gay student targeted with physical violence
finally defends himself,
但您……什么？
and you're... What?
开除他？
Suspending him?
我们可以考虑开除
We could consider suspension.
不，你不能
No. You couldn't.
我倒有兴趣看看董事会如何处置您
I'll be interested to see what the board makes of you
当这件事曝光于整个国家，更别说还有法律
when this is in front of the entire
country, not to mention our lawyers.
你打算采取这方法吗？
Do you want to sue them?
我……我不知道……
I... I don't, uh...
我们将起诉你和学校董事会
We're suing you and the school board.
我不知道他是同性恋
I didn't even know he was gay.
留校察看怎么样？
What about after-school detention?
多长时间？
For how long?
一个月
A month.
看起来还算公平
That seems fair.
留校察看
After-school detention.
我会让他去做高中毕业舞会的准备工作
We'll put him to work helping the prom committee
布置万圣节舞会
set up for the Halloween dance.
好吧我们同意
We'll agree to that
但是我不想接下来听到任何事
But I do not want to hear anything further
关于这年轻人感到疲倦了
about this young man being harassed.
我们是否说清楚了？
We understand each other?
我相信是的，先生……
I believe we do, Mr...
你是谁？
Who are you?
我是这家人的朋友
I'm a friend of the family.
留校察看一个月
After-school detention for a month.
就这样？ 是的
That's it?
Yeah.
- 回头见   - 噢，David？
See you later.
Oh, David?
我能跟你说几句吗？
Can I talk to you for a second?
我跟Luke到走廊聊一会儿，没问题吧？
I'm going to step out into the hall
with Luke for a moment, if that's okay.
噢，当然
Oh, certainly.
所以，她认为是你杀了Craig
So, she thinks you killed Craig.
并且打算去跟警察谈
And she's trying to make a case to the police
警察就会让她男朋友出来
so they'll let her boyfriend go.
- Anna告诉你的？  - 是的
Anna told you all this?
Yeah.
你也认为是我杀了Craig？
Do you think I killed Craig?
我不在乎
I don't care.
这也就是为什么
But that's why
他让我查查佛罗里达那个整容医生
she wanted me to check out that plastic
surgeon in Florida.
她想知道你跟那儿有什么联系
She wanted to know what the connection was there.
是啊，为什么我需要一个整容医生，对吧？
Yeah, I mean, why would I need
a plastic surgeon, right'?
改变你的外貌？
To change your appearance.
比如弄些骨头进去
Like, the bones in your face.
或者打磨你的手指就不会留下指纹
And maybe scar up your fingers
so you don't have prints.
至少我是这么想的
I mean, at least that's what I figured.
我知道你不是真正的David Collins
I know you're not really David Collins,
真正的可能就是Anna说的那样
I looked him up right after Anna said that.
所以你可能不想让人知道你是谁
So, maybe you don't want people to know who you are.
一个正好能干这些事的医生
A doctor who would do that sort of thing
或许就是你想要的
is probably pretty rare.
我意思，也可能不是这样
I mean, there's probably rules against it.
或者那医生可能需要钱
But that doctor, well, I guess he needs the money,
所以就做类似的事情
so he'd do that kind of work.
这是个很有趣的理论
That's an interesting theory.
我没打算告诉任何人这事儿
I'm not going to tell anyone about it.
没人会相信Anna
And nobody will believe Anna.
她没有任何证据对抗你
She doesn't have anything against you.
你也杀了爸爸的老板，对吧？
You killed Dad's boss, too, right?
我不在乎，我不会说任何事
I don't care. I'm not going say anything.
为什么不？
Why not?
因为我们是朋友
Because we're friends.
对吗？
Right?
对，当然我们是
Yeah. Of course we are.
Okay -
我只想让你知道
I just wanted you to know.
Anna有没有告诉其他人这件事？
Did Anna tell anyone else about this?
不知道
I don't know.
她的朋友，Dristen，可能？
Her friend, Kristen, maybe'?
Okay-
谢谢
Thank you.
你知道，David，我真的……
You know, David, I really...
想要谢谢你
I wanna thank you.
如果你没来这儿，真不知道我会怎样
I don't know what I would have done
if you hadn't been here.
我并非只说今天的事
And I don't... I don't mean just for today,
我是说所有的事
I mean everything.
我是……我是真心感谢
I am... I'm really grateful.
真的，Peterson夫人，这没什么
Really, Mrs. Peterson. It's no problem.
我得去歇会儿
I'll go get the rest.
谢谢你，David
Thank you, David.
请原谅，女士，你是Anna Peterson吗？
Excuse me, ma'am. Are you Anna Peterson?
不是，她在餐馆工作
Uh, no. No, she's working at the diner.
我是她妈妈
I'm her mother.
她怎么……她做了什么？
What's she... Did she do something?
不，没事，夫人
No, it's fine, ma'am.
不过你女儿，她给我们打了电话
But your daughter, she put in a call to Fort Kennilworth
几天以前，询问David Collins的事情
a couple of days ago asking about a man
named David Collins.
对，是的，她打过电话
Yes. Oh, that's right, she did.
你看见过什么人吗
You wouldn't happen to have seen anyone
类似这个人，见过么？
resembling this man, would you?
这是……David
This is, um... David.
夫人，你最后何时看见他的？
Ma'am, when was the last time you saw him.
噢，他刚刚进屋
Well, he just went inside.
No!
抓住那女人，回来这儿
Stop the girl! Get back here.
抓住他
Get him!
噢，妈的
Oh, shit!
不不，噢，David，什么……
No, no, no, no. Ah! David, what...
怎么回事，David？
What is happening, David?
这些人是谁？
Who are those men?
对此我真的抱歉，Peterson夫人
I really am sorry about this, Mrs. Peterson.
恐怕我没有完全跟你说实话
I'm afraid I haven't been fully honest with you.
你什么意思？
What do you mean?
解释起来话就长了
It would take too long to explain.
我想帮助你们
I wanted to help.
我考虑当我在这儿时，我的任务是协助你们
I considered it my mission to assist you all
while I was here.
只是事情太复杂了
There were just too many complications.
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
David，为什么这些人想杀死你？
David, why are those men trying to kill you?
没关系
It doesn't matter.
你是……
Did you...
你真的认识我儿子？
Did you even know my son?
是的
I did.
Yes.
我们曾执行同一个计划
We were in the same program.
并且他明白我必须在这儿做什么
And he would understand what I have to do here.
他在这儿在……
He's here in the...
对不起
I'm sorry.
我要进去
I'm going in.
掩护我15秒，然后控制住
Give me 15 seconds of cover, then hold.
妈的
Fuck!
Fuck.
什么……
What the...
喔喔喔
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
David.
对此我真的抱歉，先生
I'm really sorry about this, sir.
我想他死了
I think he's dead.
军事警察，我需要你的车
Military police.I'm gonna need
your vehicle.
什么？
What?
- 钥匙在车里吗？ - 是的，不过……
Are the keys in it?
Yes, but...
抱歉，你是Anna Peterson吗？
Excuse me, are you Anna Peterson?
Yes.
我是Major Carver
My name is Major Carver.
军事警察，我需要你跟我过来
Military police. I need you to come with me, please.
好的，发生什么了？
Okay. What's going on?
是关于David，Peterson小姐
It's about David, Miss Peterson.
他不是你想的那样
He is not who you think he is.
我们需要现在就走
And we need to go now.
Okay -
一切都好吗？
ls everything all right?
我想是的，我回头打给你，好吗？
I think so. I'll call you later, okay?
Peterson小姐
Miss Peterson.
Hey-
Hey.
Anna上班吗？
Is Anna working?
哦，她刚走
Um, she just left.
Oh, yeah?
她去哪儿了？
Where was she going?
不太清楚
I'm not sure exactly.
去接Luke吗？
To pick up Luke?
Um...
我想她是要去……
I think that she's going...
没关系
Never mind.
什么？
What?
好的，明白，我们这就出发
Okay. Copy. We're on our way.
什么？
What?
我们得去REC中心接你弟弟
We're going to the REC center
to get your brother.
警察不能派车过去
The police couldn't send a car there.
他们说正忙着
They've got their hands full.
好的，你必须告诉我怎么回事
Okay. You need to tell me what's going on.
你是谁？
Who are you?
什么？你是为了David过来？
What? You came here for David?
Yes.
你认识的那个叫David的士兵
The soldier you know as David
是个正在接受医学实验项目的人
was one of the subjects of a medical experiment.
我们正在对他进行研究，但他杀了几个人跑了
While we had him under study,he killed several peopleand escaped.
他烧了尸体迷惑我们
Then he burned their bodies to confuse us.
我们以为他也死在火中
We thought he'd died in the fire initially.
那是我们还以为他完了
By the time we figured out what he'd done,
没留下什么痕迹
the trail was cold.
或许你不应该
Maybe you shouldn't have tested
用精神病患者做实验
your procedures on a psychopath.
各方面看，他都是个完美的士兵
By all accounts, he was an ideal soldier.
我不知道
I don't know.
我需要给我弟弟打电话
I need to call my brother.
Peterson先生，那是手机吗？
Mr. Peterson, is that a cell phone?
我不是说过“关机”吗？
Didn't I say, "Phones off“?
交给我
Hand it over.
下课后再来拿
You can have it back after detention.
Luke，听到留言给我打电话
Luke, I need you to call me
when you get this.
好吗，这很重要
Okay? It's important.
警车这是去哪儿？
Where are those cop cars going?
你离开后有人袭击了你工作的餐馆
Somebody attacked your diner
right after we left it.
说是发生了爆炸
It was called in as an explosion.
有人活下来吗
Is anyone alive?
不知道
I don't know.
有人想制造混乱让警察保持忙碌
It's possible that he'd leave some wounded
to keep them busy.
等等，我父母在哪儿？
Wait. Where are my parents?
你还没提到过我的父母
You haven't said anything about my parents.
他们都死了
They're both dead.
在我们阻止之前他杀了他们
He killed them before we could stop him.
对不起
I'm sorry.
No.
David的神经可以自我调节，Peterson小姐
David has neurological conditioning, Miss Peterson,
旨在保护他和实验成果
designed to protect both him and the experiment.
如果他觉得事情可能败露
If he feels like his identity may be compromised,
他会程序化地清除所有麻烦
he's programmed to clean up all loose ends.
我怀疑如果需要，他是不会让自己停下来的
I doubt he could stop himself now
even if he wanted to.
这就是为什么，我们需要把你和你弟弟接到安全的地方
It's why we need to get you and your brother
somewhere safe.
Peterson小姐，我们得走了
Miss Peterson, we need to go.
Peterson小姐
Miss Peterson?
Uh...
是的，去接我弟弟
Yeah, let's go get my brother.
这是什么鬼地方？
What the hell is this?
秋季舞会，他们做的万圣节迷宫
For the fall dance, they do this Halloween maze thing.
跟紧我
Stay close to me.
妈的，里面是什么？
God damn it! What in the hell?
谁在那儿？
Who's in here?
军事警察
Military police!
我是来找Luke Peterson
I'm here for Luke Peterson.
怎么才能通过这个迷宫？
How do I get through this maze?
左，右，右，左，左
Left, right, right, left, left,
右，左，然后直走
right, left, then straight.
明白？
Got it?
Yeah.
- Luke   - 对不起……
Luke! Uh, excuse me.
你们刚打断了他的拘留过程
But you're interrupting detention right now.
你们到底是谁？
Who are you exactly?
怎么回事？
What's going on?
我们得走，你姐姐……
We need to go. Your sister...
哦，妈的
Oh, shit.
还有谁在这儿？
Who else is in here?
没人，就我们俩
No one. It's just us two.
控制灯的开关在哪儿？
Where are the lights controlled from?
控制盒在后面
There's a DJ booth in the back.
我们得离开这儿，马上。后门在哪儿？
We need to get out of here. Now.
Where's the back exit?
这边，跟着我
It's this way. Uh, follow me.
快
Come on. Uh...
就这边
Just this way.
慢点
Slow down.
快跑！去另外一边，走
Run! Go out the other way! Go!
你好，长官
Hello, sir.
你不应该来找我
You shouldn't have followed me.
我不知道你期望什么
I don't know what you expected.
妈的
Shit.
Anna，我不知道怎么回事，但David不会伤害我们的
Anna, I don't know what's going on,
but David wouldn't hurt us.
Luke，我需要你相信我
Luke, I need you to trust me.
快点
Just come on.
What?
妈的
Shit.
快
Come on.
你得藏在这儿，好吗？
I need you to hide in here. Okay?
什么？不
What? No way.
Anna，你看，David只是个才离开军队的家伙
Anna, look, David was probably
just after that army guy.
让我们只是……
Let's just...
跟他谈谈
Let's go talk to him.
Luke.
他杀了妈妈和爸爸
He killed Mom and Dad.
不，他不会，你是乱说的
No, he didn't. You're just saying that.
什么？
What?
妈妈和爸爸是……
Mom and Dad are...
Please, Luke.
好吧，你得藏在这里
Okay, you need to hide in there.
我去把他引开
I'm going to lead him away.
除非听见是我或者警察，否则别出来
You can't come out unless you hear me or the police.
我会回来找你的
I'm going to come back for you.
对此我十分抱歉，伙计
I'm really sorry about this, guys.
我讨厌采取其他方式
I tried to think of another way to do it.
或者其他办法
Any other solution.
Luke!
出来吧，老弟
Come on out, buddy.
我不会伤害你
I'm not going to hurt you.
你杀了我的父母
You killed my parents.
是的
I did.
Yes.
Ow!
别挣扎了，很快就完事
Stop it. It'll be over in a second.
Hey, Luke.
你做了正确的事
You did the right thing.
我不会责怪你
I don't blame you.
不要感觉不好
Don't feel bad.
谢谢你
Thank you.
你好吗
You okay?
是的，你呢？
Yeah. Are you?
Yeah.
跟着灯光
Follow the light.
你俩都觉得没事吗？
You both feeling okay?
我们很好
We're fine.
好的，我很快回来
Great. I'll be right back.
收到
Copy that.
怎么了？
What's the deal?
应该有两具尸体在里面
Guess there's two bodies inside,
都烧的不成样子
both of them pretty badly burned.
一个家伙说，他们的牙齿都没了
One of the guys said their teeth are missing,
糊涂了，所以我不知道是咋回事
got knocked out, so I don't know what the deal is.
一旦清理干净，你就能进去了
As soon as we get the all clear,
you can go in.
Okay -
怎么回事！
What the fuck!